[
  {
    "question": "lunch",
    "answer": "das Mittagessen"
  },
  {
    "question": "cake",
    "answer": "der Kuchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "colleagues",
    "answer": "die Kollegen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the drink",
    "answer": "das Getränk"
  },
  {
    "question": "card",
    "answer": "die Karte"
  },
  {
    "question": "board game",
    "answer": "das Brettspiel"
  },
  {
    "question": "activity",
    "answer": "die Aktivität"
  },
  {
    "question": "Spain",
    "answer": "Spanien"
  },
  {
    "question": "Italy",
    "answer": "Italien"
  },
  {
    "question": "Austria",
    "answer": "Österreich"
  },
  {
    "question": "France",
    "answer": "Frankreich"
  },
  {
    "question": "Christmas",
    "answer": "das Weihnachten"
  },
  {
    "question": "party",
    "answer": "die Party"
  },
  {
    "question": "dish",
    "answer": "das Gericht"
  },
  {
    "question": "meat",
    "answer": "das Fleisch"
  },
  {
    "question": "chicken",
    "answer": "das Huhn"
  },
  {
    "question": "beef",
    "answer": "das Rindfleisch"
  },
  {
    "question": "cheese",
    "answer": "der Käse"
  },
  {
    "question": "vegetable",
    "answer": "das Gemüse"
  },
  {
    "question": "onion",
    "answer": "die Zwiebel"
  },
  {
    "question": "carrot",
    "answer": "die Karotte"
  },
  {
    "question": "potato",
    "answer": "der Erdapfel"
  },
  {
    "question": "tomato",
    "answer": "der Paradeiser"
  },
  {
    "question": "pepper",
    "answer": "der Paprika"
  },
  {
    "question": "spinach",
    "answer": "der Spinat"
  },
  {
    "question": "oven",
    "answer": "der Ofen"
  },
  {
    "question": "pan",
    "answer": "die Pfanne"
  },
  {
    "question": "recipe",
    "answer": "das Rezept"
  },
  {
    "question": "pumpkin",
    "answer": "der Kürbis"
  },
  {
    "question": "cucumber",
    "answer": "die Gurke"
  },
  {
    "question": "eggplant",
    "answer": "die Aubergine"
  },
  {
    "question": "zucchini",
    "answer": "die Zucchini"
  },
  {
    "question": "broccoli",
    "answer": "der Brokkoli"
  },
  {
    "question": "cabbage",
    "answer": "der Kohl"
  },
  {
    "question": "spice",
    "answer": "das Gewürz"
  },
  {
    "question": "oil",
    "answer": "das Öl"
  },
  {
    "question": "salt",
    "answer": "das Salz"
  },
  {
    "question": "pepper",
    "answer": "der Pfeffer"
  },
  {
    "question": "garlic",
    "answer": "der Knoblauch"
  },
  {
    "question": "salad",
    "answer": "der Salat"
  },
  {
    "question": "wine",
    "answer": "der Wein"
  },
  {
    "question": "beer",
    "answer": "das Bier"
  },
  {
    "question": "fruit juice",
    "answer": "der Obstsaft"
  },
  {
    "question": "bottle",
    "answer": "die Flasche"
  },
  {
    "question": "country",
    "answer": "das Land"
  },
  {
    "question": "to cook",
    "answer": "kochen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to bake",
    "answer": "backen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to celebrate",
    "answer": "feiern"
  },
  {
    "question": "to buy",
    "answer": "kaufen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to play",
    "answer": "spielen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to have",
    "answer": "haben"
  },
  {
    "question": "to come",
    "answer": "kommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to work",
    "answer": "arbeiten"
  },
  {
    "question": "to make",
    "answer": "machen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to be",
    "answer": "sein"
  },
  {
    "question": "to like",
    "answer": "mögen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to cut",
    "answer": "schneiden"
  },
  {
    "question": "to fry/to roast",
    "answer": "braten"
  },
  {
    "question": "to grill",
    "answer": "grillen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to eat",
    "answer": "essen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to drink",
    "answer": "trinken"
  },
  {
    "question": "Georgian",
    "answer": "georgisch"
  },
  {
    "question": "European",
    "answer": "europäisch"
  },
  {
    "question": "expensive",
    "answer": "teuer"
  },
  {
    "question": "delicious",
    "answer": "lecker"
  }
]
